We out here fucking with Spitta and these vehicles.
I met Spitta, aka Currency, when Dame Dash opened a creative space in Tribeca, New York called DD172.
This was such a dope time for hip-hop because the convergence of the internet and then access to studios made it possible for independent artists to really do their thing.
I was there.
This space was filled with creatives and folks who were doing music, who were doing art, who were doing video.
Currency and I formed a homieship over laughs because he's one of the most hilarious people of all time.
My name is Cousin Sanse.
I want y'all to talk about...
What's going on back here?
What's this stuff?
This is just the background that, um, you know, I...
What is it?
God damn it.
It takes a lot...
Where'd you get this?
It takes a lot to get me out of my shit.
This motherfucker...
You win.
See, I'm done.
I ain't...
He was successfully carving his own lane and dropping projects and he put out This Ain't No Mixtape
and asked me to join Nicky Facts on a record called Food for Thought.
This is one of my favorite verses ever.
Big ups and spitter for always recognizing my dopeness because I always have seen it in him.
You just feelin' some kind of wind, shit.
Got my heart sweet like sour salt, west side bomb, but the spice style in my heart.
Boss likes my barack, people listen when I talk.
Start of a movement, I'm the spark that got the game in line.
Took my spot, box a lot, didn't see me comin'.
Figure like a poppin' lock, but got them boys runnin', man.
Like water they wanna, and I got it drippin'.
The lady, they buggin', they think they'll be sippin' on his neck top.
Next to greatness, empress of the rhythm.
Riding to the top, the cream of the crop.
I redeem all the liquor women like Al-Kai.
They got someone to believe in, not a black girl lost.
Now it's 2026 and I'm reclaiming my timeline.
As Amanda Diva 2.0, my new album, Truth Translator, drops June 14th.
It's not a movement, it's movement music.